Title:Who do you think you are?
Artist:Spice Girls
Genre:dance pop
steps:Super_Ray
graphics:Super_Ray
questions/comments/complaints:crazyray_21@hotmail.com
song cut: Rage*
video by/big thanks to: Rage*


bpm:118
SINGLES: B-1 L-3 S-5 H-7
DOUBLES: L-3 S-5 H-7


A SPICY STORY
----------------
If you were with s for Cheesemix 2, you may remember my account of
my love for the Spice Girls during my high school years. My favorite
Spice Girl was, of course, Emma Bunton aka Baby Spice. Anyway, this song
comes to us from thier debut album, "Spice". It was thier 3rd or 4th single
from that album. I don't actually remember it being released over here in
the US. The only singles I remember from "Spice" over here were Wannabe,
Say You'll Be There, and 2 Become 1. 


STEP INFO
----------------
SINGLES STEPS

BEGINNER 1 TAP STEPS: 58/HOLD STEPS :0
----------------
Typical beginner steps here. Nothing really worth mentioning.

LIGHT 3 TAP STEPS: 151/HOLD STEPS: 14
----------------
Just quarter note stream here. It can be fairly streamy at some points,
but nothing out of context for typical light steps. There's also some jumps
and a few holds mixed in there.

STANDARD 5 TAP STEPS: 212/HOLD STEPS: 12
----------------
A good mixture of quarter note stream and short 8th note runs
that go with vocals and bg stuff. There's a good amount of jumps and some
holds during the 2nd half of the song, to go with the bouncy, fun feel.

HEAVY 7 TAP STEPS: 272/HOLD STEPS:12
----------------
The beginning feaures some off beat notes that go with the horns.
the rest is pretty much sections of 8th runs that go with vocals
and the basic rythym/bass line. There's also some jumps and a few 
holds for added fun.

DOUBLES STEPS

LIGHT 3 TAP STEPS: 109/HOLD STEPS:18
----------------
Just quarter note stream, with some holds. The patterns are different from
light singles, and there's a few more holds.

STANDARD 5 TAP STEPS: 193/HOLD STEPS: 22
----------------
Pretty similar to singles mode, with about the same mixture of
8th and quarter stream. There are some different rythyms and different
types of patterns used than in singles mode.

HEAVY 7 TAP STEPS: 277/HOLD STEPS:23
----------------
Quite a bit streamier than singles mode. There's pretty much
a little bit more of everything here. watch out for a few 8th runs that
go across the pads.


GRAPHICS INFO
----------------
The graphics were made with paint shop pro 9. I tried to make
them bright and colorful, to match the feel of the song. The Spice Girls image
was found during a google search.